http://imamemphis.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Brendon Barrett operates imamemphis.org and may operate other imamemphis.org. It is Brendon Barrett policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our imamemphis.org.
Imamemphis.org Visitors
Like most imamemphis.org operators, Brendon Barrett collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Brendon Barrett’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Brendon Barrett visitors use its imamemphis.org. From time to time,Brendon Barrett may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its imamemphis.org.
Brendon Barrett also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on imamemphis.org blogs/sites. Brendon Barrett only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Brendon Barrett’s imamemphis.org choose to interact with Brendon Barrett in ways that require Brendon Barrett to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Brendon Barrett gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at imamemphis.org to provide a userBrendon Barrett and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Brendon Barrett are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Brendon Barrett collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Brendon Barrett. Brendon Barrett does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain imamemphis.org-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Brendon Barrett may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its imamemphis.org. Brendon Barrett may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Brendon Barrett does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Brendon Barrett discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Brendon Barrett behalf or to provide services available at Brendon Barrett imamemphis.org, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Brendon Barrett imamemphis.org, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Brendon Barrett will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Brendon Barrett discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Brendon Barrett believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Brendon Barrett, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Brendon Barrett imamemphis.org and have supplied your email address Brendon Barrett may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Brendon Barrett takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a imamemphis.org stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the imamemphis.org each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help Brendon Barrett identify and track visitors, their usage of imamemphis.org, and their imamemphis.org access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Brendon Barrett imamemphis.org, with the drawback that certain features of our imamemphis.org may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Ads
Advertising partners, who may set cookies, may deliver ads appearing on any of our imamemphis.org to users. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Brendon Barrett and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Brendon Barrett may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Brendon Barrett sole discretion. we encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a imamemphis.org account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Search for:
About Author"Legal matters are not easy to handle as it needs expertise. Once trapped in the net of legal web, it takes years to find a way out". In this blog, Brandon aims to help people in saving their time and visiting the court for hearings and getting embarrassed in the public. Popular Posts
Struggling with Finances? Here’s How Accountants Can Help
24 May , 2019
Legal Tips for Small Businesses
04 Apr , 2017
Legal mistakes that new companies make
04 Apr , 2017
Can You Cash In A Pension?
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Can You Cash In A Pension?
